

ICT-Engineer student specializing in web development. Experienced with all stages of the development. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Java, Python, c# and c++. Understanding in various frameworks and ERPs including Node.JS, React and SAP. Database know-how in SQL and MongoDB. Now studying about technologies.

PETRI MALMSTRÖM

Phone:

+358 123123123

E-Mail:

petri.malmstrom@gmail.com

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/petri-malmstrom

Skill Highlights

- Leadership
- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Out-of-the-box problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Team player

Languages

Finnish - excellent English – excellent Swedish - acceptable

Experience

01/2007 - PRESENT

Warehouse operator – Kesko

- Handling goods in all forms
- SAP experience
- System, network and app testing
- Day to day problem solving and communication
- General improvements of the workflow

01/2006 - 12/2006

Petty officer - Upinniemi

• Leading and training new recruits

Education

Attending ICT-engineer - studies, HAMK

Currently

AM-koodari, various universities of applied sciences

2020-2021

2001-2004

Upper secondary school – Oulunkylä

References

References available on request